free-codecs.com 2012-06-26

# Codecs.com :: Privacy Policy : Please read carefully this Privacy Policy before using Codecs.com / Free-Codecs.com

Privacy Policy

Please read carefully before using Codecs.com (aka Free-Codecs.com)

**This Privacy Policy only applies to Codecs.com and its mirrors.**

Codecs.com may use cookies to enhance your surfing experience, but cookies will not be used under any circumstances to personally identify you without your prior consent. If the user decides to participate in the forum, with user's consent, a cookie will be issued to keep track of the username and password for the period of 1 year. 

We will not sell, share, or rent this information. We may, from time to time, use this information to contact you - although this will happen infrequently - or to respond to questions or comments that you send us.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. 

If you have any questions, suggestions or complaints about our Privacy Policy please [contact us](http://www.free-codecs.com/contact_us.htm) immediately!
